{
    "subject": "resource/Shringar_Nagaraj",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Male_actors_in_Kannada_cinema",
    "human_readable": "Shringar Nagaraj is about male actors in Kannada cinema.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8930933475494385,
            "question": "Is Shringar Nagaraj about female actors in Kannada cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8104201555252075,
            "question": "What is Shringar Nagaraj about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7624156475067139,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of actors featured in Shringar Nagaraj?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.735964834690094,
            "question": "Which type of actors does Shringar Nagaraj focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7216007113456726,
            "question": "Who are the subjects of Shringar Nagaraj?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6291677355766296,
            "question": "Is Shringar Nagaraj a book, a film, or something else?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5923097133636475,
            "question": "What language's cinema does Shringar Nagaraj cover?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4068981111049652,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the significance of Kannada cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4046436548233032,
            "question": "What is the genre or theme of Shringar Nagaraj?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25879615545272827,
            "question": "Are there any other resources related to Kannada cinema?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Shringar Nagaraj is about male actors in Kannada cinema.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1356_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre or theme of Shringar Nagaraj?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1356_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the significance of Kannada cinema?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1356_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language's cinema does Shringar Nagaraj cover?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1356_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1356_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as all of the provided text snippets are about a person named Shringar Nagaraj who is described as an actor and/or singer in the Kannada film industry. The context also mentions that he is a male, and his involvement in Kannada cinema is mentioned multiple times throughout the text."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Shringar Nagaraj is about male actors in Kannada cinema.\" Multiple documents mention his roles as an actor in Kannada films and his contributions to the industry, which align with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple texts state Shringar Nagaraj was an actor, cameraman, and producer.  Additionally, some sources mention his work on films like \"Pushpaka Vimana\" which starred Kamal Hassan.  There's no indication the focus is exclusively on male actors.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}